Park Place, The Gallery of Art Research, Inc. and Paula Cooper Gallery
Archives of American Art, Smithsonian Institution
- Paula Cooper Gallery, 1962-2006, Series 3:; (Boxes 4-49, 51; 45.7 linear feet)
  - Artists' Files, 1962-2006, bulk mid-1970s-early 2000s, 3.3:
    - Piper, Adrian (Box 34)
      - Contract of Sale [Generali Foundation Acquisition?], circa 2000s (Box 34, Folder 7)
      - Generali Foundation Acquisition, Vienna, Austria, 2002-2003, (2 folders) (Box 34, Folder 8-9)
      - Museu d'Art Contemporani de Barcelona, Spain, 2002, 2004 (Box 34, Folder 10)
      - Institut d'Art Contemporain, Lyon, France, 2002-2004 (Box 34, Folder 11)
      - Copies of Notebooks, circa 2002-2003 (Box 34, Folder 12)
      - Publication, circa 2002-2003 (Box 34, Folder 13)
      - Documenta XI, 2001-2002 (Box 34, Folder 14)
      - European Retrospective, 2002, 2004, (5 folders) (Box 34, Folder 15-19)
      - "L'Hiver de l'Amour," Musee d'Art Moderne de la Ville de Paris, France, 1993-1994 (Box 34, Folder 20)
      - Liverpool Biennial, 1999 (Box 34, Folder 21)
      - The Color Wheel Series, 2000-2001 (Box 34, Folder 22)
      - Medi(t)Ations, 2001-2002 (Box 34, Folder 23)
      - LSD Paintings, 2002 (Box 34, Folder 24)
      - Adrian Piper Miscellaneous Texts [Photocopies], circa 1990s-2000s (Box 34, Folder 25)
    - Quaytman, Harvey, 1970-1973 (Box 34, Folder 26)
    - Quaytman, Harvey, Correspondence, 1969-1973 (Box 34, Folder 27)
    - Quaytman, Harvey, Onnasch Galerie (June 18 - Aug. 20, 1971), 1971-1973 (Box 34, Folder 28)
    - Reich, Steve and William Wiley, 1968-1972, 2006 (Box 34, Folder 29)
    - Rockburne, Dorothea, circa 1970 (Box 34, Folder 30)
    - Roldandini, Livia, circa 1969-1970 (Box 34, Folder 31)
    - Rückriem, Ulrich (Box 34)
      - Biographies, 1971-1973, 1995 (Box 34, Folder 32)
      - Exhibitions, circa 1971-1975 (Box 34, Folder 33)
    - Rückriem, Ulrich (Box 35)
      - Correspondence, circa 1971-1979 (Box 35, Folder 1)
      - Photographic Materials, circa 1970s, (2 folders) (Box 35, Folder 2-3)
    - Ruda, Edwin (Box 35)
      - Correspondence, 1966-1977 (Box 35, Folder 4)
      - Artist's Statements, circa 1965-1970s (Box 35, Folder 5)
      - Biography and Bibliography, circa 1970s (Box 35, Folder 6)
      - Collections, circa 1970s (Box 35, Folder 7)
      - Reviews, 1971-1975 (Box 35, Folder 8)
      - Exhibitions, 1960s-1970s (Box 35, Folder 9)
      - Photographs, circa 1969-1975 (Box 35, Folder 10)
      - Transparencies, circa 1971-1975 (Box 35, Folder 11)
      - Negatives, circa 1973 (Box 35, Folder 12)
      - Slides, circa 1966-1976, (2 slide boxes) (Box 35, Folder 13)
    - Sanderson, Doug (Box 35)
      - Biography, circa 1973 (Box 35, Folder 14)
      - Correspondence, 1971-1976 (Box 35, Folder 15)
      - Exhibitions and Reviews, 1973-1975 (Box 35, Folder 16)
      - Photographic Materials, circa 1970s (Box 35, Folder 17)
    - Shields, Alan (Box 35)
      - [Correspondence], 1986-1999 (Box 35, Folder 18)
      - Prints, circa 1980s-1990s (Box 35, Folder 19)
      - Johnson County Community College, Kansas, 1988 (Box 35, Folder 20)
      - Kalamazoo Institute of Arts (Thru June 1989), 1987-1988 (Box 35, Folder 21)
      - Richland College, Dallas, TX, 1988 (Box 35, Folder 22)
      - Tandem Press Documentation, 1988 (Box 35, Folder 23)
      - Nicholas Roukes, "The Art of Paper Sculpture", 1989 (Box 35, Folder 24)
      - Commission, Rudin Management Co., Inc., 1989-1991 (Box 35, Folder 25)
      - Experimental Printmaking Slides, 1978 (Box 35, Folder 26)
      - Summit Art Center, New Jersey, 1987 (Box 35, Folder 27)
      - The Standard Club, Chicago, IL, 1990 (Box 35, Folder 28)
      - Robert Kleinschmidt (Private Commission), 1990 (Box 35, Folder 29)
      - Application for Mid-Atlantic Arts Foundation Grant, circa 1990 (Box 35, Folder 30)
      - Port of Portland Proposal, circa 1989-1990 (Box 35, Folder 31)
      - Computerized Sewing Machine, circa 1980s-1990s (Box 35, Folder 32)
      - Prints, Tyler Graphics, 1980s (Box 35, Folder 33)
      - Sushi Bar, Sanchez Print, circa 1981 (Box 35, Folder 34)
      - Alaska Prints, 1989 (Box 35, Folder 35)
      - Tyler Graphics, 1986-1989 (Box 35, Folder 36)
    - Shields, Alan (Box 36)
      - Omar Account, 1970-1977 (Box 36, Folder 1)
      - Stonybrook Exhibition (1982), 1982 (Box 36, Folder 2)
      - Newspaper Clippings and Miscellaneous, 1970s (Box 36, Folder 3)
      - Commune di Milano (1979), 1979 (Box 36, Folder 4)
      - On Consignment (1974-1975), 1975-1978 (Box 36, Folder 5)
      - Gallery Ueda, Tokyo, Japan (1983), 1982-1983 (Box 36, Folder 6)
      - Paula Cooper Gallery Exhibition Lists, 1980s (Box 36, Folder 7)
      - Mobile, AL, 1980-1983 (Box 36, Folder 8)
      - Dallas Public Library, Dallas, TX, 1983 (Box 36, Folder 9)
      - Correspondence, 1970-1981, (2 folders) (Box 36, Folder 10-11)
      - NEA Art in Public Places Madison Project, 1977-1978 (Box 36, Folder 12)
      - Japan Fellowship (1978), 1978 (Box 36, Folder 13)
      - Memphis Brooks Museum of Art Exhibition, TN (1984), 1983 (Box 36, Folder 14)
      - Tyler Graphics, 1978 (Box 36, Folder 15)
      - Announcements, 1977-1983 (Box 36, Folder 16)
      - Zurich Exhibition, Switzerland (1979), 1979-1980 (Box 36, Folder 17)
      - [Snapshots of Strung Beads], circa 1972 (Box 36, Folder 18)
      - Correspondence, 1971-1985, (2 folders) (Box 36, Folder 19-20)
      - [Miscellaneous], 1987-1992 (Box 36, Folder 21)
      - Commission, The Port Authority [World Trade Center?] (1990), 1990-1994 (Box 36, Folder 22)
      - Williams College of Art Exhibition, MA (1979), 1979-1980, (2 folders) (Box 36, Folder 23-24)
      - [Lists of Works and Miscellaneous], circa 1993-1994 (Box 36, Folder 25)
      - [Correspondence, Commissions], 1987-1988 (Box 36, Folder 26)
      - Metro-Dade Art in Public Places, 1990-1991 (Box 36, Folder 27)
      - James Madison University, VA, 1987 (Box 36, Folder 28)
      - Cleveland Center for Contemporary Art, OH, 1984-1986 (Box 36, Folder 29)
      - Guggenheim Museum Proposal, 1991-1995 (Box 36, Folder 30)
    - Shields, Alan (Box 37)
      - [Correspondence], 1993-1995 (Box 37, Folder 1)
      - Exhibition Announcements, Postcards and Posters, 1970-1994, (6 folders) (Box 37, Folder 2-7)
      - Artist's Statement, 1993 (Box 37, Folder 8)
      - Selected Bibliography (assel.bib), circa 1992 (Box 37, Folder 9)
      - Selected Biography (assel.bio), circa 1992 (Box 37, Folder 10)
      - Press (1975-1994) [Photocopies], circa 1975-1994 (Box 37, Folder 11)
      - Press, Miscellaneous Reviews, circa 1978-1994 (Box 37, Folder 12)
      - Biography, circa 1995 (Box 37, Folder 13)
      - Public Collections (Paintings), circa 1995 (Box 37, Folder 14)
      - Public Collections (Paper), circa 1995 (Box 37, Folder 15)
      - Bibliography, circa 1995 (Box 37, Folder 16)
      - Magazine and Newspaper Clippings, 1973-1994, (4 folders) (Box 37, Folder 17-20)
    - Shields, Alan, Photographs (Box 37)
      - Prints (1994), circa 1993-1994 (Box 37, Folder 21)
      - Paintings and Installations (1994), circa 1993-1994 (Box 37, Folder 22)
      - Paintings and Installations (1993), 1993-1994 (Box 37, Folder 23)
      - Paintings (1992), 1992-1993 (Box 37, Folder 24)
      - Paintings and Installations (1991), circa 1990s (Box 37, Folder 25)
      - Necklaces, circa 1993 (Box 37, Folder 26)
      - Paintings (1990), circa 1990s (Box 37, Folder 27)
      - Paintings (1989), circa 1989-1990s (Box 37, Folder 28)
      - Paper (1989), circa 1989-1990s (Box 37, Folder 29)
      - Prints (1989), circa 1988-1989 (Box 37, Folder 30)
      - Paintings (1988), 1989 (Box 37, Folder 31)
      - Paper (1988), 1988-1989 (Box 37, Folder 32)
      - Paula Cooper Gallery Installation (Jan. 1988), circa 1988-1990s (Box 37, Folder 33)
      - Paper and Prints (1987), circa 1987-1990s (Box 37, Folder 34)
      - Paper (1986), circa 1986-1990s (Box 37, Folder 35)
      - Paula Cooper Gallery Installation (Jan. 1986), circa 1986-1990s (Box 37, Folder 36)
      - Paper (1985), circa 1985-1990s (Box 37, Folder 37)
      - Paintings (1985), circa 1985-1990s (Box 37, Folder 38)
      - Paintings (1984), circa 1984-1990s (Box 37, Folder 39)
      - Paula Cooper Gallery Installation (Feb. - Mar. 1984), circa 1984-1990s (Box 37, Folder 40)
      - Prints (1984), circa 1984-1990s (Box 37, Folder 41)
      - Paper and Prints (1983), circa 1983-1990s (Box 37, Folder 42)
    - Shields, Alan, Photographs (Box 38)
      - Paula Cooper Gallery Installation (Apr. 1982), circa 1982-1990s (Box 38, Folder 1)
      - (1982), circa 1982-1990s (Box 38, Folder 2)
      - Paper and Prints (1981), circa 1981-1990s (Box 38, Folder 3)
      - Paintings (1981), circa 1981-1990s (Box 38, Folder 4)
      - (1980), circa 1980-1990s (Box 38, Folder 5)
      - (1979), circa 1979-1990s (Box 38, Folder 6)
      - Paintings (1978), circa 1978-1990s (Box 38, Folder 7)
      - Paper and Prints (1978), circa 1978-1990s (Box 38, Folder 8)
      - Paintings (1977), circa 1977-1990s (Box 38, Folder 9)
      - Paper and Prints (1977), circa 1977-1990s (Box 38, Folder 10)
      - (1976), circa 1976-1990s (Box 38, Folder 11)
      - Paintings (1975), circa 1975-1990s (Box 38, Folder 12)
      - Paper and Prints (1975), circa 1975-1990s (Box 38, Folder 13)
      - Paper and Prints (1974), circa 1974-1990s (Box 38, Folder 14)
      - Paintings (1974), circa 1974-1990s (Box 38, Folder 15)
      - Rugs (1973), circa 1973-1990s (Box 38, Folder 16)
      - Paintings (1973), circa 1973-1990s (Box 38, Folder 17)
      - Paper and Prints (1973), circa 1973-1990s (Box 38, Folder 18)
      - Paintings (1972), circa 1972-1990s (Box 38, Folder 19)
      - The Divided Eye (1972), circa 1972-1990s (Box 38, Folder 20)
      - Paula Cooper Gallery Installation (Oct. - Nov. 1972), circa 1972-1990s (Box 38, Folder 21)
      - Paintings (1971), circa 1971-1990s (Box 38, Folder 22)
      - Prints (1971), circa 1971-1990s (Box 38, Folder 23)
      - Installations (1970), circa 1970-1990s (Box 38, Folder 24)
      - Paintings (1970), circa 1970-1990s (Box 38, Folder 25)
      - Paper and Prints (1969), circa 1969-1990s (Box 38, Folder 26)
      - Paintings (1968-1969), circa 1968-1990s (Box 38, Folder 27)
    - Shields, Alan (Box 38)
      - Color Photographs, circa 1972-1990s, (Oversized materials housed in Box 51, Folder 6) (Box 38, Folder 28)
      - Color Photographs, World Trade Center, 1990s (Box 38, Folder 29)
      - Photographs of Alan Shields, 1980s-1990s (Box 38, Folder 30)
      - Photographs and Negatives, Miscellaneous, 1970s-1990s, (2 folders) (Box 38, Folder 31-32)
      - Negatives, Prints and Polaroids, circa 1970s-1990s, (2 folders) (Box 38, Folder 33-34)
      - Slides, Artwork, 1990s (Box 38, Folder 35)
      - Slides, Available Works, circa 1993 (Box 38, Folder 36)
    - Shields, Alan, Transparencies (Box 38)
      - Paintings and Prints (1994), circa 1994 (Box 38, Folder 37)
      - Paintings and Paper (1993), circa 1993-1994 (Box 38, Folder 38)
      - Paintings and Paper (1992), 1990s (Box 38, Folder 39)
      - Paintings (1991), 1990s (Box 38, Folder 40)
      - Paintings (1990), 1990s (Box 38, Folder 41)
    - Shields, Alan, Transparencies (Box 39)
      - Paintings (1989), circa 1989-1990s (Box 39, Folder 1)
      - Paintings (1988), circa 1988-1990s (Box 39, Folder 2)
      - Paintings (1986), circa 1986-1990s (Box 39, Folder 3)
      - Paper (1986-1987), circa 1986-1990s (Box 39, Folder 4)
      - Paintings (1985), circa 1985-1990s (Box 39, Folder 5)
      - Paintings (1984), circa 1984-1990s (Box 39, Folder 6)
      - Paintings (1983), circa 1983-1990s (Box 39, Folder 7)
      - Drawings (1983), circa 1983-1990s (Box 39, Folder 8)
      - Drawings (1982), circa 1982-1990s (Box 39, Folder 9)
      - Paintings (1982), circa 1982-1990s (Box 39, Folder 10)
      - Drawings and Prints (1981), circa 1981-1990s (Box 39, Folder 11)
      - Paintings (1981), circa 1981-1990s (Box 39, Folder 12)
      - Paintings and Drawings (1979-1980), circa 1979-1990s (Box 39, Folder 13)
      - Paintings (1977-1978), circa 1977-1990s (Box 39, Folder 14)
      - Prints (1977-1978), circa 1977-1990s (Box 39, Folder 15)
      - Paintings (1974-1976), circa 1974-1990s (Box 39, Folder 16)
      - Prints and Drawings (1973-1974), circa 1973-1990s (Box 39, Folder 17)
      - Paintings (1972-1973), circa 1972-1990s (Box 39, Folder 18)
      - Paula Cooper Gallery Installation (Oct. 14 - Nov. 8, 1972), circa 1972-1990s (Box 39, Folder 19)
      - Prints (1971), circa 1971-1990s (Box 39, Folder 20)
      - Paintings (1969-1971), circa 1969-1990s (Box 39, Folder 21)
    - Smith, Tony (Estate of) (Box 39)
      - Advertising, 1984-1985 (Box 39, Folder 22)
      - Correspondence, 1987-1991 (Box 39, Folder 23)
      - The Brooklyn Museum, NY, 1989-1991 (Box 39, Folder 24)
      - Gilman Paper Company, 1988 (Box 39, Folder 25)
      - Westfalisches Landesmuseum fur Kunst und Kulturgeschichte, Muenster, Germany (Mar./Apr. 1988), 1987-1988 (Box 39, Folder 26)
      - Smith Paintings for Newark Museum, NJ, 1989 (Box 39, Folder 27)
      - Amaryllis [Consignments], circa 1984-1988 (Box 39, Folder 28)
      - Duck (TS19), circa 1980s (Box 39, Folder 29)
      - Die (TS10), 1988 (Box 39, Folder 30)
      - 81 More (TS57), 1970s (Box 39, Folder 31)
      - For M.S./For V.T., Denver, CO, 1973, 1987-1988 (Box 39, Folder 32)
      - Gracehoper (TS4), 1987-1988 (Box 39, Folder 33)
      - Marriage (TS6), Lippincott, 1989 (Box 39, Folder 34)
      - Smug (TS61), Lower Manhattan Cultural Council, 1988-1993 (Box 39, Folder 35)
    - Smith, Tony (Estate of) (Box 40)
      - Smug, St. John's Rotary, 1988 (Box 40, Folder 1)
      - The Snake is Out, 1991-1992, (2 folders) (Box 40, Folder 2-3)
      - Tau, circa 1988 (Box 40, Folder 4)
      - Legal, Jane Smith, 1987-1989 (Box 40, Folder 5)
      - Xavier Fourcade, Inc., New York, NY, 1984-1989 (Box 40, Folder 6)
      - Pending, 1991 (Box 40, Folder 7)
      - Pending, Fabrication and Storage, 1988-1989 (Box 40, Folder 8)
      - Pending, Long Term Loan, 1988 (Box 40, Folder 9)
      - Price List, circa 1985-1987 (Box 40, Folder 10)
      - Rights and Reproductions Permissions, 1986 (Box 40, Folder 11)
      - Joan Pachner's Tony Smith Dissertation, 1985 (Box 40, Folder 12)
      - Inventory, 1985-1987 (Box 40, Folder 13)
      - Drawings (Xeroxes), 1980s (Box 40, Folder 14)
      - Fabrication Instructions [Photocopies], circa 1980s (Box 40, Folder 15)
      - Fabrication Specification and Quotes, Lippincott, 1996 (Box 40, Folder 16)
      - Fabrications, Lippincott, Inc., 1986-1993 (Box 40, Folder 17)
      - Fabrication Costs, 1988 (Box 40, Folder 18)
      - [Correspondence], 1984-1991 (Box 40, Folder 19)
      - Proposed Retrospective (1994), 1994 (Box 40, Folder 20)
      - For??? Series (1969), circa 1990s (Box 40, Folder 21)
      - For??? Series Tour, Exhibition Description and List of Works, circa 1991-1995 (Box 40, Folder 22)
      - For??? Series Tour, Project Agreement, 1991-1996 (Box 40, Folder 23)
      - For??? Series, Correspondence, 1991-1997, (3 folders) (Box 40, Folder 24-26)
      - For??? Series, Insurance, 1995-1996 (Box 40, Folder 27)
      - For??? Series, Catalog, 1992-1993 (Box 40, Folder 28)
      - For??? Series, European Tour, 1991-1996 (Box 40, Folder 29)
      - For??? Series, Agreement and Correspondence, 1993-1998 (Box 40, Folder 30)
      - For??? Series, Legal - P. Stern/P. Huber, 1995-1998 (Box 40, Folder 31)
      - Photo Archive Project, 1982, 1995 (Box 40, Folder 32)
      - Susanne Hilberry Gallery, MI, 1994-1995 (Box 40, Folder 33)
      - IVAM Centre (Sept. - Nov. 1996), 1994-1997 (Box 40, Folder 34)
    - Smith, Tony (Estate of) (Box 41)
      - Nassau County Museum of Art, NY, 1996 (Box 41, Folder 1)
      - Smug List, 1989 (Box 41, Folder 2)
      - Marriage, Carter-Menil Human Rights Foundation, 1993-1994 (Box 41, Folder 3)
      - Willy, Munster, Germany, 1993 (Box 41, Folder 4)
      - Available Works, 1997-1998 (Box 41, Folder 5)
      - Auction Information, 1990-1991, 1998 (Box 41, Folder 6)
      - Museum of Modern Art Installation (July 2 - Sept. 22, 1998), 1997-1998, (4 folders) (Box 41, Folder 7-10)
      - Correspondence, 1982-2001, (4 folders) (Box 41, Folder 11-14)
      - [Correspondence], 1989-2000, (2 folders) (Box 41, Folder 15-16)
      - [Miscellaneous], circa 1981-1996, (2 folders) (Box 41, Folder 17-18)
      - Provenances, 1994-1999 (Box 41, Folder 19)
      - Matter of Exclusivity (Nov. 1999), 1997-2000 (Box 41, Folder 20)
      - Daniel Shapiro, 1995-1997 (Box 41, Folder 21)
      - Moondog Catalog, circa 1995-1999, (Includes 1 computer disc: 3.5") (Box 41, Folder 22)
      - Francois Pinault, Moondog, 1997-1999, (5 folders) (Box 41, Folder 23-27)
    - Smith, Tony (Estate of) (Box 42)
      - Stinger, 1999, (3 folders) (Box 42, Folder 1-3)
      - Smog (1999), 1998-2000, (4 folders) (Box 42, Folder 4-7)
      - 81 More (1970-1971), circa 1990s (Box 42, Folder 8)
      - Xavier Fourcade, Inc. Sales and Inventory, 1987 (Box 42, Folder 9)
      - Mailing Lists, 1990s (Box 42, Folder 10)
    - Smith, Tony (Estate of), Photographic Materials (Box 42)
      - Unidentified Artwork, circa 1980s-2000s (Box 42, Folder 11)
      - TS1, Bennington College Structure (1961), circa 1960s-1980s (Box 42, Folder 12)
      - TS2, Cigarette (1961), circa 1960s-2000s (Box 42, Folder 13)
      - TS3, Cross (1960-1962), circa 1960s-2000s (Box 42, Folder 14)
      - TS4, Gracehoper (1961), circa 1960s-1990s (Box 42, Folder 15)
      - TS5, Light Box (1961), circa 1960s-2000s (Box 42, Folder 16)
      - TS6, Marriage (1961), circa 1960s-2000s (Box 42, Folder 17)
      - TS7, Spitball (1961), circa 1983-2000s (Box 42, Folder 18)
      - TS8, Beardwig (1962), circa 1960s-2000s (Box 42, Folder 19)
      - TS9, Black Box (1962), circa 1960s-2000s (Box 42, Folder 20)
      - TS10, Die (1962), circa 1960s-2000s (Box 42, Folder 21)
      - TS11, For Marjorie (1962), circa 1970s-1990s (Box 42, Folder 22)
      - TS12, Free Ride (1962), circa 1960s-2000s (Box 42, Folder 23)
      - TS13, Night (1962) [empty folder], undated (Box 42, Folder 24)
      - TS14, Playground (1962), circa 1960s-2000s (Box 42, Folder 25)
      - TS15, The Snake is Out (1962), circa 1960s-2000s (Box 42, Folder 26)
      - TS16, Tower of Winds (1962), circa 1990s-2000s (Box 42, Folder 27)
      - TS17, We Lost (1962), circa 1960s-2000s (Box 42, Folder 28)
      - TS18, Willy (1962), circa 1960s-2000s (Box 42, Folder 29)
      - TS19, Duck (1963), circa 1960s-2000s (Box 42, Folder 30)
      - TS20, The Elevens Are Up (1963), circa 1960s-2000s (Box 42, Folder 31)
      - TS21, Throne (1956), circa 1990s-2000s (Box 42, Folder 32)
      - TS22, Mistake (1963), circa 1990s-2000s (Box 42, Folder 33)
      - TS23, Wall (1964), circa 1960s-2000s (Box 42, Folder 34)
      - TS24, Amaryllis (1965), circa 1960s-2000s (Box 42, Folder 35)
    - Smith, Tony (Estate of), Photographic Materials (Box 43)
      - TS25, Generation (1965), circa 1960s-2000s (Box 43, Folder 1)
      - TS26, Keys to Given (1965), circa 1960s-2000s (Box 43, Folder 2)
      - TS27, Memphis (1965), circa 1960s-2000s (Box 43, Folder 3)
      - TS28, Tau (1965), circa 1960s-2000s (Box 43, Folder 4)
      - TS29, New Piece (1966), circa 1980s-2000s (Box 43, Folder 5)
      - TS30, Dial (1967) [empty folder], undated (Box 43, Folder 6)
      - TS31, Maze (1967), 1989 (Box 43, Folder 7)
      - TS32, Moondog (1964), circa 1960s-2000s, (3 folders) (Box 43, Folder 8-10)
      - TS33, Smoke (1967), circa 1960s-2000s (Box 43, Folder 11)
      - TS34, Source (1967), circa 1960s-2000s (Box 43, Folder 12)
      - TS35, The Wandering Rocks (1967), circa 1960s-2000s (Box 43, Folder 13)
      - TS36, Arch (1968-1969), circa 1960s-2000s (Box 43, Folder 14)
      - TS37, Asteriskos (1968), circa 1960s-2000s (Box 43, Folder 15)
      - TS38, Domino (1968-1969), circa 1980s-2000s (Box 43, Folder 16)
      - TS39, Equinox (1968), circa 1960s-2000s (Box 43, Folder 17)
      - TS40, Moses (1968), circa 1960s-2000s (Box 43, Folder 18)
      - TS41, Stinger (1968), circa 1960s-2000s, (5 folders) (Box 43, Folder 19-23)
      - TS42, Trap (1968), circa 1980s-2000s, (2 folders) (Box 43, Folder 24-25)
      - TS43, Batcave (1969), circa 1960s-2000s (Box 43, Folder 26)
    - Smith, Tony (Estate of), Photographic Materials (Box 44)
      - TS44-TS52, For??? Series (1969), circa 1960s-2000s (Box 44, Folder 1)
      - TS44, For D.C. (1969), circa 1960s-2000s (Box 44, Folder 2)
      - TS45, For D.G. (1969), circa 1960s-2000s (Box 44, Folder 3)
      - TS46, For J.W. (1969), circa 1960s-2000s (Box 44, Folder 4)
      - TS47, For M.S. (1969), circa 1960s-2000s (Box 44, Folder 5)
      - TS48, For P.C. (1969), circa 1960s-2000s (Box 44, Folder 6)
      - TS49, For P.N. (1969), circa 1960s-2000s (Box 44, Folder 7)
      - Portrait With For P.N., Etc., circa 1960s-1990s (Box 44, Folder 8)
      - TS50, For V.T. (1969), circa 1960s-2000s (Box 44, Folder 9)
      - TS51, For W.A. (1969), circa 1960s-1990s (Box 44, Folder 10)
      - TS52, For J.C. (1969), circa 1960s-2000s (Box 44, Folder 11)
      - For??? Series C. Erickson Contact Sheets, circa 1990s-2000s (Box 44, Folder 12)
      - TS53, Haole Crater (1969) [empty folder], undated (Box 44, Folder 13)
      - TS54, Hubris (1969), circa 1970s-2000s (Box 44, Folder 14)
      - TS55, Smog (1969), circa 1980s-2000s (Box 44, Folder 15)
      - TS56, Bees Do It (1970-1971) [empty folder], undated (Box 44, Folder 16)
      - TS57, 81 More (1970-1971), circa 1970s-1990s (Box 44, Folder 17)
      - TS58, Light-Up (1971) [empty folder], undated (Box 44, Folder 18)
      - TS59, She (1971), undated (Box 44, Folder 19)
      - TS60, For Delores (1973), circa 1970s-1990s (Box 44, Folder 20)
      - TS61, Smug (1973), circa 1970s-2000s, (3 folders) (Box 44, Folder 21-23)
      - TS62, Flat Piece (1975) [empty folder], undated (Box 44, Folder 24)
      - TS63, Fourth Sign (1975-1980), circa 1990s-2000s (Box 44, Folder 25)
      - TS64, Ten Elements (1975-1979), circa 1970s-2000s (Box 44, Folder 26)
      - TS65, Lippizaner (1976), circa 1970s-1990s (Box 44, Folder 27)
      - TS66, One-Two-Three (1976), circa 1990s-2000s (Box 44, Folder 28)
      - TS67, Throwback (1976-1979), circa 1970s-2000s (Box 44, Folder 29)
      - TS68, Last (1979), circa 1970s-2000s (Box 44, Folder 30)
      - TS69, Atlanta (1980), circa 1980s-2000s (Box 44, Folder 31)
      - TS70, Five C's (1980) [empty folder], undated (Box 44, Folder 32)
      - TS71, Row One (1980) [empty folder], undated (Box 44, Folder 33)
      - TS72, Row Two (1980) [empty folder], undated (Box 44, Folder 34)
      - TS83, Tetrahedron (1961), 1992 (Box 44, Folder 35)
      - TS84, Wingbone (1962), 1992 (Box 44, Folder 36)
      - TS86-SC, Arm (1969), circa 1960s-2000s (Box 44, Folder 37)
      - TS90-SC, Trunk (1969), circa 1960s-2000s (Box 44, Folder 38)
      - Paintings Inventory, 1987-1988 (Box 44, Folder 39)
      - One Gate (Drawing for Stinger), circa 1998 (Box 44, Folder 40)
      - Drawings, circa 1993-2000s (Box 44, Folder 41)
    - Smith, Tony (Estate of), Photographic Materials (Box 45)
      - Paintings, circa 1980s-2000s (Box 45, Folder 1)
      - Paintings at Paula Cooper Gallery, Not Available, circa 1980s-2000s (Box 45, Folder 2)
      - Paintings Available, circa 1990s-2000s (Box 45, Folder 3)
      - Paintings Not Available, circa 1980s-2000s (Box 45, Folder 4)
      - Installation, circa 1985-1994 (Box 45, Folder 5)
      - Polaroids of Installation: Socrates, circa 1980s-1990s (Box 45, Folder 6)
      - Installations, circa 1970s-2000s, (2 folders) (Box 45, Folder 7-8)
      - Whitney Biennial, circa 1970s-1980s (Box 45, Folder 9)
      - Miscellaneous, circa 1970s-2000s (Box 45, Folder 10)
      - Negatives, circa 1970s-2000s (Box 45, Folder 11)